[

  {"question" :  "SPHS is poor", "Answer" :  "True"},
  {
    "question":  "AP Computer Science is the best class ", "Answer" :  "True"},
  {
    "question":  "Math is fun ", "Answer" :  "False"},
  {
    "question":  "Mr.Papadakis is a living meme ", "Answer" : "True"},
  {
    "question":  "An apple is an orange ", "Answer" :  "False"},
  {
    "question":  "JAVA is superior to all other codes ", "Answer" :  "True"},
  {
    "question":  "Issac's Asian girlfriend ditched him over the summer ", "Answer" :  "True"},
  {
    "question":  "Bulgaria is a nice country", "Answer" :  "False"},
  {
    "question":  "Issac drinks ranch sauce ", "Answer" :  "True"},
  {
    "question":  "Mr.Shorr is the GOAT ", "Answer" :  "True"}


]